<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Uncategorized &#8211; Matthew Souden</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/uncategorized/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Portfolio +</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 23:53:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/dog-badge-3.svg</url>
	<title>Uncategorized &#8211; Matthew Souden</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Modern Firm</title>
		<link>/uncategorized/the-modern-firm/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[msouden]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2015 11:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=5057</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[I was contracted by The Modern Firm to build out the custom responsive components to WordPress themes for their clients using their own in-house theme framework. It was modular, production-oriented theme building with custom styling to match the design and be responsive/mobile-friendly. Working with them was a great learning experience in the niche WordPress site business. [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>I was contracted by <a rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.themodernfirm.com/" data-type="URL" data-id="https://www.themodernfirm.com/" target="_blank">The Modern Firm</a> to build out the custom responsive components to WordPress themes for their clients using their own in-house theme framework. It was modular, production-oriented theme building with custom styling to match the design and be responsive/mobile-friendly. </p>



<p>Working with them was a great learning experience in the niche WordPress site business. Very smart folks doing powerful work. I had a hand in theme components of about 10 client sites over just a short time.</p>



<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Personal Development Seminars</title>
		<link>/uncategorized/personal-development-seminars/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[msouden]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2008 05:33:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clients]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[portfolio]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[WordPress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[work]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://msouden.com/matt/personal-development-seminars/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[PDS is &#8220;a service provider for Courts, Prosecutors, Probation and Parole agencies providing behavior change intervention utilizing the Motivational Facilitation Method, a style of communication that moves our Participant towards change in a manner that does not inadvertently create roadblocks to the Behavior Change process.&#8221; Their web site needs included the ability to manage content [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-114 alignleft" title="pds-screencap" src="http://msouden.com/wp-content/uploads/2009/06/pds-screencap2.png" alt="pds-screencap2" width="287" height="179" align="right" />PDS is &#8220;a service provider for Courts, Prosecutors, Probation and Parole agencies providing behavior change intervention utilizing the Motivational Facilitation Method, a style of communication that moves our Participant towards change in a manner that does not inadvertently create roadblocks to the Behavior Change process.&#8221;</p>
<p>Their web site needs included the ability to manage content themselves, maintenance of class schedules, mapping to class locations, class registration capabilities, and to match existing promotional materials. Utilizing a highly customized WordPress installation, custom secure forms, an embedded public Google Calendar for scheduling and mapping, and embedded custom HTML in pages, I was able to meet all of these objectives under budget.</p>
<p>Most importantly, however was the ability to do sophisticated administration through two highly intuitive interfaces &#8211; Google Calendar and the WordPress Administrative panel. The next stage for PDS will be to add transparent and secure payment and registration verification through a service provider.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Reality Counseling Services</title>
		<link>/uncategorized/62-2/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[msouden]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2006 03:44:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clients]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[portfolio]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[work]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://msouden.com/matt/62/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Reality Counseling Services is a client that I landed while working for Ideal Solution. In truth I had little to do with the development of their site, and left Ideal before the full technology plan was realized. The reason I’m adding it is because I began to get some project management stripes by learning from [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p align="left"><a title="reality_counseling_screencap.jpg" href="http://msouden.com/wp-content/uploads/2007/08/reality_counseling_screencap.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="http://msouden.com/wp-content/uploads/2007/08/reality_counseling_screencap.jpg" alt="reality_counseling_screencap.jpg" width="310" height="226" align="left" /></a>Reality Counseling Services is a client that I landed while working for <a title="idealso.com" href="http://idealso.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ideal Solution</a>. In truth I had little to do with the development of their site, and left Ideal before the full technology plan was realized. The reason I’m adding it is because I began to get some project management stripes by learning from Jeff Lawton at Ideal Solution how develop a technology plan which makes sense for a client’s particular needs, and how to work with the client to fulfill the plan over time. It’s a great example of fulfilling many different client needs with limited means. In a nutshell, the plan was as follows:</p>
<p>1. Build a web site &#8211; this is a straightforward Joomla CMS installation. This was a case where Joomla was a smart choice because while it presents a greater training challenge and ramp-up, the client will later on be able to provide a secure section for delivery of documents to constituents. We also consulted on and discussed the possibility and legal requirements in providing secure access to confidential medical information through the site. The privacy guidelines the company works within are more stringent than HIPAA due to the nature of the client’s work, and were being worked through as I departed.</p>
<p>2. A multiple-location VoIP phone system. Ideal Solution was to host the phone system at their data center. If I recall correctly the savings from separate monthly bills for five locations was roughly going to pay for the initial costs of the new web site. (If I’m wrong on this someone ping me and I’ll correct this.)</p>
<p>3. Phase three was to put into place an open source medical records deployment on a terminal sever network. While this phase of the plan was in it’s earliest stage of development, the developers were investigating <a title="VISTA project" href="http://www.worldvista.org/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">the VISTA project</a> and <a title="OpenEMR" href="http://www.openemr.net/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">OpenEMR </a>as options to centralize, improve, and secure the flow of records throughout the company. This was most likely to be housed at the company’s headquarters and be maintained by Ideal staff, which provided increased security. The plan made provisions for leasing new equipment which would most likely have been used to build a network of terminals which ran on one central server.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Another Ann Arbor</title>
		<link>/uncategorized/another-ann-arbor/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[msouden]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2006 15:37:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clients]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[freelance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[portfolio]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[work]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://msouden.com/matt/another-ann-arbor/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Another Ann Arbor is a small local nonprofit who&#8217;s stated goals is to &#8220;provide a means of communication for the African American community in Washentaw County. This is a web site where information is shared and matters of common interest can be discussed.”I was brought on to develop community awareness and participation with the organization. [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p align="left"><a title="anotherannarbor_screencap2.jpg" href="http://msouden.com/consult/wp-content/uploads/2008/02/anotherannarbor_screencap21.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="http://msouden.com/consult/wp-content/uploads/2008/02/anotherannarbor_screencap21.jpg" alt="anotherannarbor_screencap2.jpg" width="258" height="279" align="left"></a>Another Ann Arbor is a small local nonprofit who&#8217;s stated goals is to &#8220;provide a means of communication for the African American community in Washentaw County. This is a web site where information is shared and matters of common interest can be discussed.”I was brought on to develop community awareness and participation with the organization. Over the couple of years of periodic work with its founder and with the assistance of Dr. Larry Gant at the UM School of Social work we were able to achieve several goals. These included;</p>
<p>A web site redesign to include a custom CMS-like dynamic back-end which allows for volunteer-based content generation.</p>
<p>I consulted on designing the information architecture, the functionality of its back-end, A3’s organizational needs and goals for the site, graphic design, and acted as liaison between the board and the site developer Michael Spaly.I also wrote content for the site and trained board members on using the publishing capabilities.Promotional materials, press releases, and creation of a newsletter and a database of recipients.Building, obtaining funding for, and acting as program manager for an after school science program for local 6th-8th grade students. This included writing and being awarded grant funding from Pfizer Community Grants and the Ann Arbor Community Foundation. The program leveraged an NSF-developed after-school science curriculum called Science Quest.</p>
<p>My work with A3 was very rewarding and my first introduction to leveraging my marketing background to produce effective technology tools.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
